Welcome to the FDOrganizer.
You are currently on the start page of a pre-ingest tool
that will help you to prepare your research data
for the long term availability in the best possible way.
To get started, switch to the Editor tab.
Here you can collect and merge your data from different sources,
such as external databases or electronic lab notebooks.
You can also structure or curate your data and
add further relevant metadata.
In the third tab, the archive tab,
you can add the necessary legal information and have
your data package reviewed by a data curator.
If you are registered as a data curator,
you will find another tab, the review tab.
This is where you can check the data packages and,
if necessary, give some feedback to the data provider
before you can submit the data to the long-term archiving system.
Please refer to the individual steps for more information on the exact procedure.